All right let's now deal with when someone
reaches to the far side of your body
whether it's to your far side leg or
far side of your head and as
you see as we talked about earlier so
when the arm's here I can attach
it when he takes it to
the far side so either to
my head here okay or looking
for like grips here or going to
these these grips like this trying
to scoop it with my left arm
like I've been doing it's going
to be really busy.
And it's just not going to work.
Okay.
So I can still get it I will
end up scooping with my left arm.
But I just have to do it.
A slightly different way.
Okay.
So we'll go from the hands on the
shins first so that's pretty common
way people will toriando as they
or work towards north-south.
Okay.
So what I do here keep my knees tight.
Actually sorry.
And I should say we're going
to go through the reverse joy
bar which deals with this
in a slightly different way.
But for now we're just
going to try and pass
it back to the regular joy bar okay.
So from here if I can as he goes around
I'm going to fold up grab the tricep
grab the wrist pass the arm above my head
and take my head out the other side.
Okay.
And you'll see as I do that
I'm starting to fold
it into my into my
elbow if possible right ideally
here it's possible you end up
like even just next to your
head which is not as good
as I talked about before.
But ideally we get it folded around
that you know we're bending their elbow
and folding it around our own elbow
getting some of that shoulder pressure.
Right okay once we're there we're in
our regular finishing position.
Okay.
So again Jayden goes
from north-south start.
So he's going normal he changes his hand.
Right I go elbow wrist.
I take my head to the
other side so you have to like
duck your head under as you grab
your grip so we're here.
And we can look for the finish
if he changes to the far side of
my head it's similar so he grabs
the far side of my head.
It's just probably a little
bit more jammed up.
Okay.
But I grab the wrist I grab it I
want to have my knees ready to frame.
So if he tries to close the
gap in to pass that's difficult okay
as I take my head to
the other side right this one.
I'll probably just get it stuck on
the head but that's okay.
I'm trying to keep some
some frame and some distance
usually on this one because we're in north
south you can chop straight to the armpit
you don't need like there's no
point chopping the head
here you might do the
knee down for a moment if you need to.
But if we've got access to chop
straight to the armpit okay.
And we look for the finish.